https://github.com/VU-MICHAEL

michaelvu1811@gmail.com

4 Crabapple Court, Brantford, Ontario, N3R 5X9

Michael Vu

Objective:

I am a reliable, respectful, and motivated university student with interest of building experience in the workforce. I am able to learn new tasks quickly, proficient in growing key customer relationships, and can handle tasks effectively and efficiently with great attention to detail.

SKILLS

- Excellent written and spoken communication skills.
- Good at following tasks
- Knowledge of useful design patterns.
- Fast learning ability
- Strong teamwork skills
- Proficient at working in a team and individually

EXPERIENCE

07/2019 - 09/2020	 Summer Student TCBA Member, Toyota Boshoku Woodstock, Ontario Performed well under a constantly stressful environment Worked as part of a successful team Performed tasks well that required great attention to detail
02/2021 - 09/2021	Dairy/Frozen associate, Walmart Brantford, Ontario
	Working in fast-paced environment
	 Stocking dairy/frozen and maintaining shelves
	 Demonstrated strong interpersonal skills while dealing with customers
	Organizing skids
07/2019 - 09/2020	Bakery Clerk, Zehrs Brantford, Ontario
	Working in fast-paced environment
	 Keep bakery stocked up, rotate products, and scan out expired product.
	Organizing freezer and skids

EDUCATION

Graduated 2020	High School Diploma, St Johns College Brantford, Ontario
2021 - Present	Bachelor of Science in Computer Science , Wilfrid Laurier University Waterloo, Ontario

REFERENCES